You are being attacked by an autonomous drone.
你正被自动无人机攻击
We don't know.
我不到啊
让我们寻思寻思先
We're still figuring that out.
You are running out of time.
不过你倒是快似了
We will show you what to do to increase your chances for survival.
我们会尽我们所能
For as long as we reasonably can.
告诉你该怎么做
Don't worry,
别急,
yet.
先别急
That's just the surveillance drone.
那只是侦察机
它走在最前面以侦察整个区域, 定位目标并评估副本难度
It goes ahead and scouts an area to locate targets and assess defences.
It's technically harmless.
理论上来讲这玩意伤不了你
But what follows it isn't.
但跟在它后面的攻击性有点强
And it's closing in on your location.
且, 它们马上就到你家门口
Get to cover immediately.
马上去找块地挖三填一
Good thing that door was strong enough.
恭喜, 门够硬
You bought yourself time.
你可以晚点再似
I will take this chance to explain.
我正好来绍介绍介
What you just encountered was a pair of modified FPV drones.
刚刚找上门的是一对大技霸魔改版FPV
FPV or first-person view drones are cheap,
FPV, 即第一人称视角,
lightweight and extremely fast.
特点是便宜、敏捷
Reaching speeds of up to 140 kilometers an hour,
最快能跑到140km/h
they are agile enough to strike a variety of targets.
不仅能板载经典地标双子塔, 还能追上移动中的车辆
Including static targets and moving vehicles.
泛用性极强, 综合强度属于超大杯
The motors give off a characteristic screech that sounds like this.
其电机会发出一种独特的尖啸声, 且听龙吟:
Typically piloted by drone operators using VR goggles,
这种无人机由佩戴VR头显的操作员操控
they hunt and respond based on a real-time video feed.
通过实时视频画面做出反应
FPV drones are often deployed in a hunter-killer pair.
FPV常成对出现
Like a sniper team, one drone is responsible for surveillance,
如狙击小队一般,
the other for pulling the trigger.
一个标点一个开枪
Surviving that first strike is commendable.
bro活过了一阶段,
Good job.
bro是这个👍
But your hiding spot is compromised.
但你的藏身处暴露了
Other drones are incoming.
第二波无人机马上到你家门口
You must move to a safe spot.
该跑路了
Now.
GKD
Your only chance is getting to the nearest city.
想活命就进城
Somewhere that has a military presence.
找个有驻军
Jammers.
干扰机
Anti-aircraft guns.
防空炮
Missiles.
防空导弹
Bunkers.
以及碉堡的地儿
But you need to survive long enough to get there.
不过你得先确保自己能活着爬到那里
Grab some gear, whatever you have on hand.
拾点手边的装备
Ski goggles, a helmet and a thick leather jacket.
譬如滑雪镜, 头盔, 以及厚皮衣
To shield you from debris or shrapnel from drone impacts.
别让自己被无人机板载产生的破片伤了
A small powder-based fire extinguisher can at least cover sensors,
再整点小型干粉灭火器
or create a smokescreen.
直喷对面摄像头, 或者给自己打给烟
Done?
完事了?
Go.
润!
Get into a vehicle and drive as fast as possible.
拾辆车去开拉力吧
Wait.
不对, 别急
Is that a chicken coop?
那是个鸡笼吗?
Good.
俺拾嘞
Destroy it and place it on top of that car.
给它拆了装车上
If you can't stay concealed,
要是没法隐匿行踪
staying protected is the next best thing.
当个铁王八也不赖
Get in.
开润
Damn.
请输入文本
That was quick.
对面够快
The drones above you are trailing a thin strand.
你头顶的无人机拖着根光纤
Up to 30 kilometers worth of fiber optic line.
总长高达30千米
They must know that you are heading for the city.
对面一定知道你想润进城
These drones don't rely on radio signals.
这些无人机不是用无线电遥控的
They are hardwired to the operator.
它们与操作员通过光纤传输信号
Impossible to jam.
不会被无线电干扰机干扰
But they are louder, slower,
不过相比无线款, 它们更慢更吵
and the wire can get tangled.
线也可能被缠住
Head for the forest.
往森林里开
That's one.
一架寄了
And that's two.
第二架也out了
Ouch.
艹
Are you alive?
没似?
Good.
挺好
You added a layer of protection that one drone could not get through.
拾来的鸡笼立了大功
The car and chicken coop cover have bought you some time.
它挡住了一架无人机
For now.
让你多活了几分钟
别急
More drones are coming.
还有高手
The closer you get to the city,
离城市越近
the more sophisticated the systems will be.
副本难度越高
They are optimized to avoid human error.
它们经过优化, 以在一定程度上避免人为失误
Drive as fast and far as you can.
快给地板油
We'll take this time to explain.
是这样,
In 2013, MIT engineering students launched the Perdix system.
2013年, 麻省理工学院工程系的学生发布了山鹑无人机系统
参见: 求闻百科 或 中文维基百科 [[山鹑 (无人机)]]
A small, low-cost UAV that can be deployed in large numbers.
这种无人机小型, 低成本, 可被大规模部署
原视频: File:DOD 103983712-1024x576-1769k.webm
They launched 103 Perdix drones from three F/A-18 Super Hornets.
仅仅3架F/A-18就能扔103架山鹑
The drones operate with a distributed brain,
allowing them to change conditions without centralized control.
The Perdix drones share data,
have no single leader,
and reconfigure when drones are added or removed.
By 2015, the Office of Naval Research revealed a low-cost UAV swarming technology,
also known as LOCUST.
A tube-based launcher for releasing small,
unmanned autonomous vehicles in rapid succession.
The LOCUST program was the precursor for drone swarms.
In theory, hundreds of small autonomous UAVs could cost less than a single tactical
aircraft, while also being more effective and robust.
Unmanned systems were force multipliers.
One agent could, in theory,
control significantly more assets in battlespace.
A swarm could also coordinate.
They operate most commonly in waves.
The surveillance wave gathers information across large areas.
This involves mapping the environment,
identifying and location potential targets,
detecting enemy defense,
and providing persistent information for commanders.
To do this, the surveillance wave uses coordinated search patterns.
These include, but are not limited to,
random walks, creeping lines,
expanding squares, grid-based,
and two-step search and survey.
By flying at layered altitudes,
they ensure coverage in both vertical and horizontal space.
For persistent surveillance,
they may loiter in the surrounding perimeters,
with drones cycling in and out in pulses.
Once surveillance is gathered,
the second wave starts.
The key objective of this wave is to destroy and suppress the enemy's defense.
Once defenses are overwhelmed,
the last wave begins.
The strike wave.
Speed up.
You're so close.
That looks painful.
Can you run?
You're almost there.
Wow.
I really thought you were a goner.
There must be a jammer close by.
They emit a powerful radio frequency signal that severs critical inter-drone communication links
Overwhelming their GPS navigation across a wide area.
Some advanced systems even use high-power microwaves...
to disrupt the electronic systems of multiple drones simultaneously.
Time to get to that bunker.
快
Quickly.
该进地堡了
Do you hear that?
你听到轰鸣声了吗?
That low rumble is the AVIC Jiu Tian.
那是中航工业的"九天"
This 10-ton Chinese mothership is designed to carry and deploy drone swarms...
这架10吨重的国产无人机"母舰"
across vast distances.
有着长达25米的翼展
With a 25-metre wingspan...
专为远距离投送大量小型无人机设计的巨兽
it operates at altitudes of 15,000 meters,
能在15000米的高空飞行
far beyond the range of most air defences.
大多数防空手段远不可及
Its 7,000-kilometre range means it can launch from deep within enemy territory...
其长达7000千米的航程
and still reach its target.
Each Jiu Tian carries up to 100 smaller drones...
in internal payload bays.
When multiple motherships coordinate...
they can cover thousands of square kilometres simultaneously.
The sub-drones share information instantly...
creating a connected network that adapts to changing conditions.
What makes this system particularly effective is scale.
Individual countermeasures become irrelevant...
when facing hundreds of coordinated drones.
Standard survival tactics no longer apply.
These narrow streets are providing good cover.
It's too late to get to the bunker...
but you have time to hunker down in one of these buildings.
Get in!
Quick!
Drone swarms can achieve mass destruction...
through the accumulation of many small-scale attacks.
They are a fundamental shift in weapons technology.
Modern wars are described as unmanned hellscapes...
where an offensive swarm campaign...
would meet a counter-swarm of drones.
At this point, no place is safer than any other.
Any door you barricade is a door that can be destroyed.
Your survivability depends on one thing...
Who is sending the attack?
When a human controls a drone...
there are inherent limitations.
Reaction time averages 200 to 300 milliseconds...
for complex decisions.
Fatigue degrades performance after extended operations.
Moral hesitation can delay or prevent engagement.
A human pilot might miss a target...
due to stress or poor visibility...
might choose not to fire on ambiguous targets...
might make tactical errors under pressure.
These human weaknesses can become...
your survival advantages.
You can exploit predictable behavior patterns.
Confuse operators with decoys...
or unexpected movements.
Force them into situations...
where human judgment becomes a liability.
But artificial intelligence operates...
by different rules.
An AI can process visual data in microseconds.
They don't experience fatigue,
fear or moral conflict.
Executing mission parameters with mathematical precision.
If you are designated as a target...
it will pursue you with unwavering focus.
20 to 60 euros.
And this whole concept of evolution is true...
is the realtà...
efficiency of human intelligence...